[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mummy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
Peppa Pig.
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA: Stars.
NARRATOR:
It is almost time for bed.
Mummy Pig, Daddy Pig and Peppa
are having mugs of hot milk.
[SNORTS THEN GIGGLES]
George, why are you dressed up
in that spacesuit?
You should be
in your pajamas.
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
George loves
everything to do
with space.
Oh.
[GIGGLES]
George,
take your space helmet off
to drink your milk.
[SLURPS THEN BURPS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Bedtime, little ones.
[GEORGE & PEPPA LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
At night, George likes
to listen to his space mobile.
[LULLABY MUSIC PLAYING
OVER MOBILE CHIMES)
Not space again.
[SIGHS]
It's boring.
Space isn't boring.
It's full of stars.
[SNORTS]
I can't see anything.
It's too dark.
It's easier to see the stars
from outside.
Can we go outside now?
Peppa,
you're in your pajamas.
Maybe if you put your coats on
over your pajamas,
we could go outside
just this once.
Hooray!
[SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLES]
Daddy, why are you lying
on the ground?
This is the best way
to see the stars.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
DADDY PIG:
Look at these little stars.
Imagine
you are joining the dots.
MUMMY PIG:
That's called the Big Dipper.
PEPPA & GEORGE:
Ooh.
DADDY PIG: Yes.
And the two stars at the end
point to the North Star.
PEPPA & GEORGE:
Wow.
♪ North Star, North Star ♪
♪ Are you near
Or are you far? ♪
♪ Can we get there
In the car? ♪
Ho-ho-ho. No, Peppa.
The stars
are much too far away.
Are they even further
than the seaside?
Oh, yes.
But they look a lot closer
through a telescope.
Have we got a telly-scope?
[SNORTS]
No,
but Grandpa Pig
has a very good telescope.
Can we go
to Grandpa Pig's house now?
Ho-ho-ho.
It's much too late.
[SNORTS]
Maybe we can go
just this once, Daddy Pig.
Hooray.
NARRATOR:
It is the first time
Peppa and George have been
in the car at night.
[♪♪♪]
[SNORTS]
Look, we're following
the North Star.
[PEPPA CHUCKLES]
♪ North Star, North Star ♪
♪ Shining
With a twinkly glow ♪
♪ Please show us
The way to go ♪
[ALL LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George have arrived
at Granny
and Grandpa Pig's house.
Oh, dear.
I do hope
Grandpa and Granny Pig
haven't gone to bed.
[DOORBELL DINGS]
What are you doing here
at this hour?
We want to see the stars.
Peppa and George were hoping
they could look
through your telescope.
I see. Very well.
To the top of the house,
everyone.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Here she is.
Old Bess.
BOTH:
Wow.
NARRATOR:
Grandpa Pig's hobby
is looking at the stars.
Now,
who's for the first look?
Me, me, me!
Ooh. The North Star.
We sailors use it
to find our way home.
Daddy used it
to find his way here.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Are there other things
in the sky?
Yes.
This is a planet called Saturn.
PEPPA: Wow.
What are those pretty rings?
GRANDPA PIG:
They are made of rock and ice.
Saturn is very, very cold.
PEPPA: We could build
a snowman, George.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Quick. Look.
Oh.
GRANDPA PIG:
It's a shooting star.
You must make a wish.
I wish that when George is old
enough to have his own rocket,
he will take me into space.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
Daddy Pig's Birthday.
NARRATOR:
Today is Daddy Pig's birthday.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig has to go to work.
Daddy, I wish you didn't have
to work on your birthday.
Ha, ha. So do I.
But I'll be home
as soon as I can.
See you later.
ALL: See you later.
[HORN HONKS]
[SNORTS]
While Daddy Pig is at work,
we can get all
his birthday surprises ready.
[BOTH LAUGH]
First, we'll make
Daddy's birthday cake.
We start with butter,
and sugar and flour.
Then we add an egg.
And most important of all,
the chocolate bits.
BOTH: Ooh.
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig is making
a chocolate cake.
Daddy Pig loves
chocolate cake.
I give it a stir.
Mummy, can I stir?
Yes, Peppa.
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves stirring.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
George wants a go.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
Okay, George,
that's enough stirring.
There.
Daddy Pig's chocolate cake.
PEPPA:
Hooray!
Now, we just have to bake it
in the oven.
[SNORTS]
Mummy, can I lick the spoon?
Yes. You can lick the spoon,
and George can lick the bowl.
Yippee.
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love
chocolate cake mixture.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Poor Daddy Pig,
he's missing all the fun.
Mummy, can I ring Daddy at work
and say, "Happy birthday"?
That's a nice idea.
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGS]
NARRATOR:
This is the office,
where Daddy Pig works.
Hello, Mr. Rabbit speaking.
May I speak to Daddy Pig,
please?
Someone for you, Daddy Pig.
It sounds important.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Daddy Pig speaking.
Happy birthday, Daddy!
[SNORTS]
Happy birthday!
Ho, ho. Thank you, Peppa.
Don't be late home, Daddy.
[SNORTS]
Bye-bye.
Bye-Bye.
[BOTH BLOWING PARTY HORNS]
BOTH:
Happy birthday, Daddy Pig.
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
[♪♪♪]
[SNORTS]
There's just
one more thing
to do
before Daddy gets home.
Yes.
Daddy's birthday surprise.
[GIGGLES]
Shh. George, remember,
it's a secret.
Shh.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George have
buckets of water.
Mummy Pig has balloons.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
I wonder what Daddy Pig's
birthday surprise can be.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Daddy's home.
Quick. Back to the house.
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is home from work.
ALL:
Happy birthday, Daddy Pig.
[BLOWS PARTY HORN]
[LAUGHS]
Thank you, everyone.
[SNORTS]
Wow. What a lot of candles.
That's because
you're very, very old, Daddy.
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
You must blow out
all your candles in one go.
Ho, ho. I'll do my best.
[INHALES DEEPLY
THEN EXHALES AUDIBLY]
ALL:
Hooray!
[SIGHS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS] And here's
your birthday present.
Thank you.
[THUDDING]
New boots. Fantastic.
Let's try them out.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Peppa, George and Mummy Pig
are wearing their boots.
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is wearing
his birthday boots.
Daddy Pig has found
a little puddle.
Let's see
if these boots work.
NARRATOR: The puddle is a bit
too little for Daddy Pig.
Hm.
What I need is a big puddle.
Heh. Why not try over here,
Daddy Pig?
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
Ooh. What's this?
It's your special
birthday surprise.
[GIGGLES]
Shh.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
What are they up to?
[SNORTS]
A big muddy puddle.
Fantastic.
[LAUGHS]
My birthday boots
work perfectly.
[SNORTS]
Would you care to join me
in my birthday muddy puddle?
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
Everyone loves jumping up
This is my best
birthday ever.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
Sleepover.
NARRATOR:
It is nighttime.
Peppa is going
to a sleepover
at Zoe Zebra's house.
[SNORTS, THEN GIGGLES]
Hello, Zoe.
Hi, Peppa.
Welcome to my sleepover.
I'll pick you up
in the morning.
Bye-bye, Peppa.
Bye.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Rebecca, Suzy and Emily
are already here.
Hello, everyone.
ALL:
Hello, Peppa.
I've got my teddy.
"Hello, everyone."
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Zoe has her toy monkey.
[GIBBERS]
Emily has her frog.
[CROAKS]
Suzy has her owl.
[HOOTS]
And Rebecca has her carrot.
"Carrot, carrot."
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Mr. Zebra
is watching television.
[CAR ENGINES WHIRRING]
That's better.
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
I was watching that.
But it was a bit boring,
Daddy.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Daddy Zebra
is going to bed now.
He has to get up early
to deliver the post.
Very well, Mummy Zebra.
Don't stay up too late.
Good night, Mummy.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends
are getting
into their sleeping bags.
Zoe's baby twin sisters,
Zuzu and Zaza,
want to join
the sleepover too.
[BOTH WHINNY]
The sleepover is only
for big girls.
[BOTH CRYING]
Aw, they're so sweet
and little.
Can they stay?
Okay. But you must promise
you'll stay awake.
BOTH:
We promise.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Wow. A piano.
I'm having lessons.
Listen.
♪ Twinkle, twinkle
Little star ♪
[PLAYING OFFKEY NOTES]
Can I have a go?
ALL: And me.
ALL: ♪ Twinkle, twinkle
Little star ♪
[PLAYING OFFKEY NOTES]
♪ How I wonder
What you are ♪
Shush. You must be quiet
so Daddy Zebra can sleep.
Now, into your sleeping bags,
please.
[♪♪♪]
[SNORTS]
What do we do now?
On sleepovers,
there's always a midnight feast.
What's a midnight feast?
We eat things in secret.
ALL: Ooh.
I know where there's food.
But we must be very quiet.
[♪♪♪]
[SUZY & PEPPA GIGGLE]
Shh, Suzy.
Shh, Peppa.
Quiet.
NARRATOR:
Mummy Zebra has woken up.
[SNORTS]
We're going to have
the best midnight feast
ever.
[ALL LAUGH]
What's going on?
You'll wake Daddy Zebra.
Now, who knows a nice,
gentle bedtime story?
Me.
ALL:
And me.
I'll start.
Once upon a time,
there was a little fairy.
Now your turn, Peppa.
And she lived in the forest.
She was very pretty...
And she had a fairy wand.
Lovely.
Your turn, Emily.
Tell us what happens next.
Well, I'm not really sure.
Just say anything, Emily.
As long as it's not boring.
Okay.
The little fairy met
a big monster, who went...
[TRUMPETS]
[ALL SHRIEK]
Too scary.
[ALL LAUGHING]
What's all this noise?
NARRATOR: Oh, dear.
The noise has woken Mr. Zebra.
Sorry, Daddy.
There was a story
about a fairy.
And a scary monster.
And we want to know
what happens next.
Very well.
[CLEARS THROAT]
The monster lifted up
his big, hairy paws
ALL: Ah.
And walked along
on his big, hairy feet.
ALL: Ooh!
And he said:
♪ Twinkle, twinkle
Little star ♪
[PLAYING SONG PERFECTLY]
♪ How I wonder
What you are ♪♪
[ALL SNORING]
NARRATOR: Mr. Zebra's song
has sent everyone to sleep.
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
Cold Winter Day.
[WIND WHISTLING
THEN PEPPA QUIVERS]
NARRATOR:
It is very cold today.
Peppa and George are wearing
their hats, scarves, coats,
mittens, and boots.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING]
Look, George.
The trees haven't got leaves.
NARRATOR: In the winter time,
the trees lose their leaves.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
have found a muddy puddle.
BOTH: Ooh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love
jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[SNORTS]
Me first.
Aah! Ugh!
NARRATOR: It is so cold,
the puddle has turned to ice.
It is very slippery.
[LAUGHS]
It's not funny.
[CHUCKLES]
NARRATOR:
Here are Mummy Pig
and Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
Oh, good, a muddy puddle.
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig loves jumping
in muddy puddles.
Stop, Daddy.
Whoa!
[ALL GASP]
Ho-ho-ho. That was close.
Lucky, I've got
such a good sense of balance.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Daddy,
the puddles are icy today.
We can't jump in them.
[SNORTS]
Never mind.
Let's feed some bread
to the ducks.
BOTH:
Hooray! Hee-hee-hee.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love
feeding the ducks.
[QUACKING]
[SNORTS]
Hello, ducks.
We've got some bread
for you.
[QUACKING]
NARRATOR:
The ducks like bread.
[PEPPA GIGGLES]
Oh.
NARRATOR: It is so cold,
the pond has frozen to ice.
[QUACKING]
NARRATOR:
The ice is very slippery.
[ALL LAUGH]
Sorry for laughing,
Mrs. Duck.
But it did look quite funny.
[QUACKS]
[QUACKING]
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
It is starting to snow.
Snow!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love snow.
[SNORTS]
George, let's catch snowflakes.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are catching snowflakes.
Ooh.
NARRATOR:
George has caught a snowflake.
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
Peppa has caught a snowflake.
Ooh.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[BLEATS]
NARRATOR:
Here is Suzy Sheep
on her toboggan.
Whee!
[LAUGHS]
Hello, Peppa.
Wow! Suzy, that looks fun.
[BLEATS]
We're all tobogganing
on the big hill.
There's lots of snow there.
[LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Shall we climb up the big hill
and watch the tobogganing?
Yes, please.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[BLEATS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Peppa's friends are
tobogganing on the big hill.
Whee!
[BARKS]
Yahoo!
[GIGGLES]
Whoa!
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
George has slipped
on the hill.
You look funny, George.
[GIGGLES]
NARRATOR: George does not think
it is funny.
[CRYING]
It's quite easy
to slip on the hill.
Maybe I should carry George.
Daddy, can you carry me too?
Ho, ho. All right, Peppa.
Just be careful
you don't slip over, Daddy Pig.
Ho, ho.
Don't worry, Mummy Pig.
Remember, I've got
an excellent sense of balance.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[BARKS]
Let's have a race.
ALL:
Yes!
Ready, steady, go!
ALL: Whee!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Here we are.
The top of the big hill.
[SNORTS]
Do be careful
you don't slip, Daddy Pig.
[LAUGHS]
I'm not going to slip.
Whoa!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Daddy is like
a big toboggan!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Yahoo!
Whoa!
Whee!
We're going to win the race!
Hooray!
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are the winners.
ALL:
Well done, Peppa!
[SNORTS]
My Daddy makes
a very good toboggan.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
It's not funny.
It is a bit funny,
Daddy Pig.
Hm.
I suppose it is quite funny.
[LAUGHS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING AND SNORTING]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS THEN GIGGLES]
[SNORTING AND GIGGLING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS AND GIGGLES]